The Making of 'Rebecca' is a documentary film directed by Lisa Van Eyssen.
Documentary on Alfred Hitchcock's 1941 film "Rebecca" and the
working relationship of Hitchcock and producer David O.
Self, played by Rudy Behlmer.
Self, played by Peter Bogdanovich.
Self, played by Bruce Dern.
Self, played by Leonard Leff.
Self, played by Stephen Rebello.
Self, played by Richard Schickel.
Rebecca Alie O'Connell (née Romijn  roh-MAYN, Dutch: [roːˈmɛin]; formerly
Romijn-Stamos; born November 6, 1972) is an American actress and former model.
She is known for her role as Mystique in the original trilogy (2000–2006) of the X-Men film series, as Joan from The Punisher (2004) (both based on Marvel Comics), the dual
roles of Laure Ash and Lily Watts in Femme Fatale (2002), and Una Chin-Riley on Star Trek: Discovery (2019) and Star Trek: Strange New Worlds (2022–present).
She has also had a recurring role as Alexis Meade on
the ABC television series Ugly Betty.
Her other major roles include Eve Baird on the TNT series The Librarians, voicing Lois Lane in the DC
Animated Movie Universe, and as the host of the reality competition show Skin Wars.